wowko.com 2006-11-16

# Wowko,Buy wow gold,world of warcraft gold,Lineage II Adena,EverQuest II,EvE Online,FFXI Gil,Star Wars,Diablo II Items and more.....

### ACCEPTANCE OF TERMS

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of the terms of Wowko's Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site and exit the Site immediately. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean that you accept those changes.

### INFORMATION SUBMITTED AND COLLECTED; USE OF INFORMATION

#### Personal Information

When you use Wowko.com (the "Site"), we will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you, such as your name, address, telephone numbers, and email address. Generally this information is requested when you make an online purchase,equest technical support, or submit ideas or suggestions. When making online purchases or when establishing a credit line account with us, we will also collect financial information, such as your credit card number and expiration date, bank and credit references.

#### Use Of Personal Information

We use your personal information for the following primary purposes:

  * to make the Site easier for you to use by not having to enter information more than once;
  * to complete online purchase transactions and process applications for a credit line account; 
  * to respond to your technical support requests; 
  * to remember the contents of your shopping cart from session to session so that you may continue shopping where you left off;
  * to evaluate and respond to your ideas or suggestions;
  * to analyze your use of the Site and purchases of our products to make our marketing efforts more effective and improve our product offerings to you;
  * From time to time, we may also alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new services from Wowko, unless you request otherwise.

Unless otherwise stated on the Site, Wowko will not share your personal information with other companies except for associated financial institutions in order to verify credit information for an online purchase or establishment of an account. Wowko will disclose your personal information only in special cases, such as (i) to comply with valid legal requirements, such as a law, regulation; or (ii) when Wowko has reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who, intentionally or unintentionally, may be causing injury or harm to Wowko.com users or other persons or violating the Terms and Conditions of Use for this Site.

In the event that Wowko, or any component of Wowko's operations, is merged with, or is acquired by, another entity, then any such successor or acquiring entity may become the successor to our obligations with respect to the personal information that you have provided to Wowko, which would be necessary for the entity to effectively continue Wowko's business. By using this Site, you consent to any such use of your personal information by such an entity assuming control of Wowko's operations as a result of a merger, purchase of Wowko assets, or liquidation of Wowko in bankruptcy or insolvency.

You can use most of the Site without providing personal information; however, you will need to provide personal information in order to make online purchases, request literature or technical support, or see product price and availability information.

If you do not want Wowko to communicate with you about other offers regarding Wowko products, programs, events, or services by e-mail, postal mail, or telephone, you may select the option when prompted stating that you do not wish to receive marketing messages from Wowko.

### Non-Personally Identifiable Information

#### Internet Protocol (IP) Address

Your current IP address (72.20.99.48) has been stored.  
Your information is safe with us!

#### Cookies

When you enter the Site, we create your profile, assign a personal identification number, then send this personal identification number back to your hard drive in the form of a cookie, which is a very small bit of code (a few kilobytes) that contains no personal information. This code is uniquely yours and allows you to navigate the Site without having to fill out registration forms with information you have already provided as long as you are using the same computer from which you initially supplied the information. Two other cookies are also written to your hard disk at various times you are navigating our Site that allow us to remember what is in your on-line shopping cart and provide you with the proper pricing for your location. Additionally, if you are interrupted before finalizing an on-line purchase, your order contents will be preserved for up to two weeks. Your credit card number is not retained in our database. Should you delete these cookies from your computer, you would simply have to provide your contact information again where a form is presented and you would lose the contents of your shopping cart. Should you decide to set your browser to reject cookies, you can still browse the Site, but on-line ordering and item prices will not be available.

We do not engage in list selling or "cookie swapping" with other companies.

### lINKS

This Site contains hyperlinks to other sites. Wowko is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites, including any sites that may indicate a special relationship or partnership with Wowko. The linked sites may collect personal information from you when you link to the site. This collecting of information is not subject to Wowko's control. To ensure protection of your privacy, always review the privacy policy of the sites you visit by linking from our Site.

### SECURITY

Wowko has taken strong measures to protect the security of your personal information and to ensure that your choices for its intended use are honored. We take strong precautions to protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction. During online ordering, sensitive information.

### NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES

This Privacy Policy may be revised over time as new features are added to the Site or as Internet security and privacy standards evolve. We will post those changes prominently so you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone. We do, however, recommend that you read this Privacy Policy each time you use the Site, in case you missed our notice of changes to the Privacy Policy.
